Amanda Steele Show. Today's Pingo Pingo. Ashanti Tuggles is a black hair stylist who
sewed an air tag into her cousin's braids before her solo trip to Mexico. Her cousin wanted some
extra security, especially with all the concerns about safety for black women traveling alone. So
Ashanti said, let's step it up and attach that air tag like it was just another hair accessory.
It's sad that a black woman had to go to these lengths to feel safe, but nothing says innovation
like a black woman who loves to travel. One thing we will do is find a way.
Goes to a Baltimore principal who's found himself in hot water after someone dropped a supposed
voice recording of him spewing racist nonsense. But guess what? The recording was faker than a
Tupac verse on a Drake diss track. Oh man, for real? It was AI. It was cooked up by a high school
athletic director in Maryland named Darian. How did they find out it was AI? Apparently
there was an investigation. The recording caused so much chaos that the principal got ganked out
of school. Mind you, the whole beef between them started because Darian was being reprimanded for
poor work performance and mishandling of school funds. So Darian got caught while trying to skip
town, was arrested at an airport security check. Where was he going? I mean, he's probably going to
Mexico, but without an air tag sewed into his brain because he did not want them to find him.